<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE chapter PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN"
                 "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">
<sect2 id="system.action.format-if-elseif-else">
    <title>FormatIfElseifElse-Action</title>

    <para>
        The FormatIfElseifElse-Action formats if, else and elseif.
    </para>
    <para>
        <literallayout>
            The option spaceAfterIf specifies if there is a space after the T_IF.
            The option spaceAfterElseif specifies if there is a space after the T_ELSEIF.
            The option spaceAfterElse specifies if there is a space after the T_ELSE.
            The option spaceBeforeElseif specifies if there is a space before the T_ELSEIF.
            The option spaceBeforeElse specifies if there is a space before the T_ELSE.
            The option breakAfterCurlyBraceOfIf specifies if there is a break after the curly-brace behind T_IF.
            The option breakAfterCurlyBraceOfElse specifies if there is a break after the curly-brace behind T_ELSE.
            The option breakAfterCurlyBraceOfElseif specifies if there is a break after the curly-brace behind T_ELSEIF.
            The option breakBeforeCurlyBraceOfElse specifies if there is a break before the curly-brace behind T_ELSE.
            The option breakBeforeCurlyBraceOfElseif specifies if there is a break before the curly-brace behind T_ELSEIF.
            The option breakAfterIf specifies if there is a break after the complete if-expression.
            The option breakAfterElse specifies if there is a break after the complete else-expression.
            The option breakAfterElseif specifies if there is a break after the complete elseif-expression.
            The option breakBeforeElse specifies if there is a break before the T_ELSE.
            The option breakBeforeElseif specifies if there is a break before the T_ELSEIF.
            The option spaceBeforeIfExpression specifies if there is a space before the expression of the if.
            The option spaceAfterIfExpression specifies if there is a space after the expression of the if.
            The option spaceBeforeElseifExpression specifies if there is a space before the expression of the elseif.
            The option spaceAfterElseifExpression specifies if there is a space after the expression of the elseif.
        </literallayout>
    </para>
</sect2>